<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alpha Church</title>
    <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alpha Church</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.dgcoc.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Update</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/covid/</guid>
      <description>Updated June 28, 2020 Starting July 5, the sequence of services will be as follows: at 9am, we will meet for the sermon and Lord&amp;rsquo;s Supper at the building. This will stream on our YouTube channel as well. Bible class will run from 10:30am to 11:15am on Zoom. Hopefully this will give more people the opportunity to gather in person and also participate in Bible class.
If you have symptoms, please stay home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 Lord&#39;s Supper</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/lordssupper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/lordssupper/</guid>
      <description>Preparing the Lord&amp;rsquo;s supper in 2020          January Angie   February Laura P.   March Pat   April Susan E.   May Marion &amp;amp; Lyna   June Karen   July Sharon R.   August Anna &amp;amp; Margaret   September Dianna &amp;amp; Ashlyn   October Laura P.   November Jen &amp;amp; Cathy   December Rebecca &amp;amp; Samantha    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 Lord&#39;s Supper Topics</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/topics/</guid>
      <description>Listed below are the suggested topics to be used in leading the Lord&amp;rsquo;s supper. You are to develop the topic to have about a 5-minute talk on the subject. The intention is for a focused talk to center our minds on why Jesus came to die and what He accomplished at the cross.
January           5 So that we might be made righteous Rom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/about/</guid>
      <description>What To Expect We desire to worship God in spirit and in truth (John 4:24). It is our desire to speak the truth of God in its entirety. As the apostle Peter said in 1 Peter 4:11, &amp;ldquo;If anyone speaks, he should do it as one speaking the very words of God.&amp;rdquo;
Singing Just like the first century Christians we read about in the Bible, we will sing psalms, hymns and spiritual songs (Eph 5:19).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2020 Responsibilities</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/responsibilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/responsibilities/</guid>
      <description>For the Month         Assignment responsibilities: Frechmann   Announcements: C. Ashton   Collection (count and post): J. Brinkley &amp;amp; Cann    Greeters/Visitor Card Pickup    Week of: MAR 1, 2020 MAR 8, 2020 MAR 15, 2020 MAR 22, 2020 MAR 29, 2020     East door D. Ashton K. Copeland Cann Elam T. Hill   West door T.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>