<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>families on Alpha Church</title>
    <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/tags/families/</link>
    <description>Recent content in families on Alpha Church</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 10:05:49 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.dgcoc.org/tags/families/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Remember Your Father</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/remember-your-father/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/remember-your-father/</guid>
      <description>As the tender years quickly pass by don’t fail to tell your father of your love for him. He loves to hear your dreams and cares and if you ask him why it may bring tears to your eyes. Fathers’ hearts are such that they want their children to be happy and safe from all the traps and snares of the world that seem so evil.
It takes but casual conversation to make images of his children flash before him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Are Mothers Made Of?</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/what-are-mothers-made-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/what-are-mothers-made-of/</guid>
      <description>There used to be a saying about what little boys and little girls are made of. The boys were said to be made of “snips and snails and puppy dog tails” - while little girls were made of “sugar and spice and everything nice, and there always seemed to be a bit of truth to those sayings.
Today, the second Sunday in May, designated as Mother’s Day, the focus is on what Mothers would be made of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marriage Commitment</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/marriage-commitment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/marriage-commitment/</guid>
      <description>Our traditional wedding ceremonies are all about formalizing a covenant relationship. In this type of covenant, the parties are identified by typical phrasing “Do you &amp;hellip; “ and names the people involved. The obligations are then given both generally and specifically, to have and to hold from this day forward, for better or for worse, for richer, for poorer, in sickness and in health, to love and to cherish &amp;hellip;” .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>