<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bob Alley on Alpha Church</title>
    <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/writers/bob-alley/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bob Alley on Alpha Church</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 10:05:49 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.dgcoc.org/writers/bob-alley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Possessed</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/possessed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/possessed/</guid>
      <description>Life has many hazards and traps that can discourage and confuse the sternest of characters. Disease is a major concern of all, but parents are especially hurt when a child suffers from complicated medical problems. Behavior changes when these known maladies are dealt with, but unexplainable or unaccountable modifications in behavior and speech bring all sorts of speculation for the causes or reasons that brought it on. As if someone or something needs to be blamed for the changes being experienced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memorial Day</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/memorial-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/memorial-day/</guid>
      <description>Remembering things is often difficult. Our memory system is weak. Even though some may claim that they may have a photographic memory time is not their friend. Trying to remember specifics can be challenging. Names and dates sometimes need repetition to recall them properly. God has recognized man&amp;rsquo;s need for such reminders.
Deeds and actions done years ago fade from memory quickly because they are so seldom brought to mind. Acts of bravery, kindness and generosity are fresh but for a short while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marriage Commitment</title>
      <link>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/marriage-commitment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dgcoc.org/posts/marriage-commitment/</guid>
      <description>Our traditional wedding ceremonies are all about formalizing a covenant relationship. In this type of covenant, the parties are identified by typical phrasing “Do you &amp;hellip; “ and names the people involved. The obligations are then given both generally and specifically, to have and to hold from this day forward, for better or for worse, for richer, for poorer, in sickness and in health, to love and to cherish &amp;hellip;” .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>